moneydashboard.com 2016-10-31

# Privacy - Money Dashboard

## Privacy and Cookie policy

This is the privacy policy for The One Place Capital Limited (trading as Money Dashboard), a company registered in Scotland (company number SC301187) with a registered office at 5th Floor, 125 Princes Street, Edinburgh, EH2 4AD (“we”, “us”, “our”) in relation to the use of personal information provided in relation to the use of the website and online account and personal finance management services provided at [www.moneydashboard.com](https://www.moneydashboard.com/) (“the Service”).

We know that you’ll want to know exactly what information we gather about you as a user of our Service (“User”), and how we intend to use (and just as importantly, not use) that information.

We'll try to keep everything in this document as straightforward as possible, but if there’s anything you don’t understand or you’re not happy about, or if you just want to suggest improvements, please get in touch with us by:

  * Emailing us at [info@moneydashboard.com](mailto:info@moneydashboard.com)
  * Writing to the Chief Executive Officer, Money Dashboard. CodeBase. Argyle House. 3 Lady Lawson Street. Edinburgh EH3 9DR

Money Dashboard has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through [www.moneydashboard.com](https://www.moneydashboard.com/).

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organisations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us as indicated above. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

### Information Which We May Collect

You do not have to supply any information simply to visit the site.

To register to use our service you will have to supply us with personal information. “Personal Information” means information that identifies you. The personal information we collect to register you is your e-mail address. In order to add your financial accounts, you will also need to provide your UK postcode and date of birth, and choose a secure question and answer. If you use our functionality to refer a friend, we will collect their email address from you. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [support@moneydashboard.com](mailto:support@moneydashboard.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. Once you have aggregated accounts with us (see “Other people who have to be able to access your information” below for an explanation) , we will have access to that account information. 

We keep track of the internet addresses from which Users visit us, and track the page(s) on our site that you visit. We analyse this data for trends and statistics. Please see “Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies”.

### How we use your information

We will use the personal information which we collect for the purposes of registering you as a User of our services, correspondence, or participating in online surveys to help us enhance our services and products for you, and to send a one-time email to your friends about our site upon your request.

We also ask for personal information at the point at which you add a financial account to enable us to ask security related questions if you later ask us to reset your password.

In addition, through a computer system-run process, we will use your personal information and information from your account aggregation for the purposes of analysing it and making suggestions which may enable you to make savings or consider alternative or additional products to the ones which you are using. These suggestions can be delivered either in the service or by way of email or text messages to you. This may involve us sending limited details about you (which will not identify you) to our partners so that we can tailor suggested products for you more accurately.

Any information we collect is used to improve the content of the site, enhance Users' experiences when visiting our site, and customise the content and/or layout of our pages.

We also use personal information in performing statistical analysis of Users’ behaviour as a whole; and to help in the creation of anonymised statistical data which we may use at our discretion (including licensing to third parties).

We do not share personal information for any reason that is not disclosed in this Policy or apparent to you at the time the information is requested and we do not sell or rent any personal information.

### Other people who have to be able to access your information

We use a company called Yodlee Inc. ([www.yodlee.com](http://www.yodlee.com/)) to provide software that lets you add details of the accounts which you want to include in the service (“account aggregation”). When you aggregate an account Yodlee collects and securely stores your log in details, such as User name and password. This information is never stored by us nor subsequently disclosed to us and is subject to Yodlee’s privacy policy. For further information on how Yodlee keeps your information secure please visit <http://yodlee.com/yodlee-security/>. Yodlee are headquartered in the USA. They have provided account aggregation to top UK & USA financial institutions for more than 10 years. We have a contract with Yodlee which requires them to be bound by our privacy policy and to meet the requirements of the Data Protection Act in just the same way as it applies to us.

### The information we may give to or share with somebody else

We may have to disclose your personal information, if required by law to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or similar legal requirement.

We may share your personal information in the following ways:

  * to companies that provide services to help us operate the application and communicate with users. These companies are authorised to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us;
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, or investigate fraud;
  * if Money Dashboard is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information;
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

### Access to or deleting your account

If you want to terminate your agreement, email [support@moneydashboard.com](mailto:support@moneydashboard.com) using the email address you used when registering for the service. Your account will be closed and your ability to log in deactivated within 30 days. 

To access and change your personal information, you should log in to your online account on our website and make the necessary changes.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [support@moneydashboard.com](mailto:support@moneydashboard.com) . We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

### How long we keep your data

Once deleted by you the data will be promptly deleted from our systems and we will subsequently be unable to access it.

We reserve the right, however to continue to use any anonymised statistical data which we created during your use of the Service.

### Use of email and text

You can use the service to provide you with email and text alerts to provide you with useful information, e.g. your current account is close to becoming overdrawn. You can disable these alerts at any time by removing these alerts from within your Profile.

We may use email or text in relation to administrative matters, e.g. sending you a replacement password, or to let you know about changes to the service. An example of this would be a proposed change to this Privacy Policy.

We will not email or text you in relation to promotional matters without your consent, other than explained in our terms and conditions. You can withdraw this consent at any time by contacting us as above or by following unsubscribe instructions within the email.

### Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our website which may contain personal information. We obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@moneydashboard.com](mailto:support@moneydashboard.com). 

### Blogs/Forums

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@moneydashboard.com](mailto:support@moneydashboard.com) . In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

Our blog is managed by a third party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please see their [security policy](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy).

### Security

Please see our full security policy at https://www.moneydashboard.com/security/

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Links to Other Websites

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the “Share this" button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address or which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Behavioral Targeting/ Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may need to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, prior to the change becoming effective, we will tell you by email, or by a notice on our homepage so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

The Money Dashboard website uses cookies to enhance your experience of our website. Cookies are small data files which are placed on a website visitor’s computer or mobile device and are stored on the hard drive. The information contained within cookies can only be read by our server. They cannot be used to read or gather personal information that you have not specifically entered yourself.

In order to access our website’s full features all cookies must be enabled. For more information on how to manage cookies please refer to our “How to manage cookies” section below.

Our use of cookies provides us with general (non-personal) information about how visitors use this website, i.e. the pages which are viewed most often or the most common traffic sources to our website. Cookies are also used across this website to remember customisable user selections to provide you with a more personalised experience.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyse trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We may link this automatically-collected data to personal information in order to allow analysis of the effectiveness of marketing campaigns How to manage cookies.

Your internet browser’s security settings or preferences enable you to take control of the information you share online. These can usually be found within your browser’s menu tab. You will be presented with the option to accept all cookies, receive an alert when a cookie has been set, or to disable your browser from receiving cookies.

Internet browsers provide the above features in their own distinct ways, so please refer to the help section – located on your browser’s menu – for a specific set of instructions on how to change your cookie preferences. For those viewing this website on a mobile device, please refer to your handset guide or technical manual.

Please remember that disabling your browser from accepting cookies may limit your ability to access our website’s full set of features and/or page content.

The use of cookies by our partners is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access to or control over these cookies.

Our third party partners employ clear gifs (also known as Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We may tie the information gathered to our Users’ personal information in order to analyse the effectiveness of marketing campaigns.

Our website also contains cookies set by third party websites (i.e. Social networking sites such as Twitter), which provide information and/or services on the MDB website. In order to manage these cookies you will have to visit the websites of our third parties and adjust your settings accordingly.

More information on how to control or manage cookies can be found at <http://aboutcookies.org/>.

Last updated: 16th January 2016.
